

- **0**9298172574
- Parada, Sto. Domingo, Ilocos Sur

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sep 2023 - Sep -2024

Field Architect

@ E.E.Black LTD

May 2021 - May 2023

Apprentice Architect

@ Ar. Cabello Design & Build

Feb 2020 - Apr 2021

Architectural Draftsman

@ Jinge Trading & Dev. Inc.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN ARCHITECTURE

University of Northern Philippines 2014 - 2019

EXPERTISE & SKILLS

- HTMLCSS
- Time Management
- Critical Thinking
- Javascript
- Problem Solving
- React
- Well-organized
- Node.js
- Team player
- Mongoose
- Workflow Management

REFERENCE

JENNIFER CORTEZ - EE Black Ltd Project In - Charge JCortes@eeblackph.com

DENNIS CABELLO - Ar. Cabello Design & Build Mentor 09157776035

LIEZEL BUENO PORCIA - Jinge Trading & Dev. Inc. HR Manager ezelfrancisco525@gmail.com

SYAN V. TORRES

Architect turned aspiring Web Developer

PROFILE

I am a licensed architect with years of experience in design and construction. Now, I am channeling the same passion for creativity and problem-solving into software development.

My mission is to combine my design expertise with modern code to build innovative digital solutions. By integrating architectural precision with the fluidity of software, I aim to create intuitive, visually striking, and highly functional applications that redefine user experience.

CERTIFICATES

HTML & CSS

- LinkedIn Learning HTML Essential Training
- LinkedIn Learning CSS Essential Training
- FreeCodeCamp Responsive Web Design

JAVASCRIPT

- LinkedIn Learning Learning the JavaScript Language
- FreeCodeCamp Javascript Algorithms and Data Structures

REACT & REDUX

FreeCodeCamp - Front End Development Libraries

NPM, NODE.JS, MONGOOSE

FreeCodeCamp - Back End Development and APIs

PROJECTS

You can check the Projects I created during my learning journey in coding together with the downloadable PDFs of my certificates on my Portfolio Website at:

**** https://portfolio-navy-delta-22.vercel.app/ ****